The ITTOs of integration
management, now we're
discussing direct and
managed project work process.
So page 90 in your PIMBOC to follow along.
So now we are moving into the executing
process group.
Now we're going to do the work according
to the plan.
And this is where we will create work
performance data.
These are our actuals.
They're called raw observations of
measurements taken during executing.
So again, we're doing the work of the
project according to the plan.
So our inputs, the project management
plan.
As soon as we create it, it's an input to
every other process.
It tells us how we will go
through our process groups,
taking our project from
beginning, initiating to end.
What else comes in project documents?
I'm not going to list
them all when you guys
have gone through the
entire course material.
You want to come back and go
through these integration processes
because then we will have
discussed creating these documents.
First go around, it's going to be a little
too much for you.
All right.
But big here will be approved change
requests.
So once we have completed planning,
so we'll develop the project management
plan, plan all of the other pieces of our
puzzle, those subsidiary plans,
then we go through the rest of the
planning processes like collecting
requirements to finding the scope,
creating the WBS.
We will keep planning until we have our
initial references for our three baselines.
Scope.
Scope always has to be established first
and agreed upon.
Based on the scope of the project that's
being agreed upon, we'll figure out how
long it's going to take, schedule
baseline, how much it will cost,
the cost baseline.
Those baselines will become components of
our project management plan.
They will be added to it.
So your plan will state what you're
setting out to accomplish, how you'll do
your processes as well as include,
your baseline scope time and cost so we do
have three separate baselines altogether
they make up the performance measurement
baseline for your project all right so
that will come in your project documents
but the big piece will be the approved
change request that's why i kind had to
step back a little bit we are baseline we
would have completed our planning
processes and at least our initial
references for scope, time, and cost,
we are baselined.
Then you move into executing to do the
work of the project.
Now, if anything has to change,
adding or deleting scope, taking
corrective preventive action, defect
repair, these approved change requests
will have to go to perform integrated
change control process.
We will cover that shortly.
That's where every change request will be
reviewed for an impact.
assessment, we'll look for alternatives to
a cost-benefit analysis.
Each change request will either be
approved, rejected, or delayed,
deferred by us, the sponsor, or CCB,
change control board.
If a change request is approved,
all that's documented in the change log.
We'll update plans and documents
accordingly.
And there's a reason I'm holding up three
fingers.
I will show that when we get to perform
integrated change control.
They go hand in hand.
If a change request is
approved, you have to update any
plans, baselines that are
impacted, and any documents.
All right.
So the approved change
request will come here to
direct a managed project
work to be implemented.
This is where we will make that change.
Then you have those EFs and OPAs.
You're going to see them coming in
throughout all the planning and all our
integration processes tools and techniques
again we'll use expert judgment we use
that project management information system
it has all our scheduling information all
our performance information in it and all
the softwares we're using and of course
we're having meetings we live in meetings
status review meetings all right so the
output of director-managed project work
the ultimate goal will be those
deliverables Because again, we're in
executing, this is the whole crux of that
process group, is to ultimately create the
deliverables.
We probably won't create them day one,
but that will be our ultimate goal.
Along the way, we will create work
performance data, the actuals,
like number of change requests,
number of validation cycles, actual start
dates, actual finish dates, actual costs,
for example.
Along the way, we also create the issue
log.
We move into executing.
This is where we're going to start having
problems, gaps, inconsistencies.
So we have an issue log, three pieces.
It will list the issue, who is supposed to
resolve it, and by when.
Issues left unresolved can become risks to
our projects.
We don't want that.
And it's our job to make sure we and our
team to make sure
issues are being resolved.
Along the way, we will also create change
requests.
We start a house Reno.
We pull out a tub.
Find out there wasn't a water barrier.
Water has been leaking through the walls.
There's now mold all over and leaking down
to the structural beams below.
We don't know how that second floor hasn't
fallen in.
So you have to have a change request the
scope is going to change okay so with that
change request it still has to go to
perform integrated change control if the
change request is approved update any
plans baselines impacted and any documents
baselines can definitely be affected they
all affect each other and documents the
requirements the resources are going to
change for example we also will contribute
to the OPAs so Remember, OPAs,
we follow the policies, procedures,
guidelines, we pull from the knowledge
repository.
Well, all along, we will contribute to the
OPAs as well.